http://www.balistreriwine.com/terms-of-service-and-privacy-policy/

Terms of Service and Privacy Policy – Balistreri Vineyards
Skip to content
We are in the process of moving all Wine Club Memberships online! If you are having trouble logging in or getting your discount, please call us at (303) 287-5156
Balistreri VineyardsTraditionally Handcrafted Natural WineHomeAboutShop Wines All WinesFeatured & On SaleRed WinesWhite WinesOrange WinesDessert WinesGifts & MoreLibrary WineLunch MenuGift BasketsWine Club My AccountReset PasswordFeatured Wines of the MonthEvent CenterUpcoming EventsContactMy Account LoginOrder HistoryGift CardsPayment methodsAccount details
0
0
Menu Close HomeAboutShop WinesAll WinesFeatured & On SaleRed WinesWhite WinesOrange WinesDessert WinesGifts & MoreLibrary WineLunch MenuGift BasketsWine ClubMy AccountReset PasswordFeatured Wines of the MonthEvent CenterUpcoming EventsContactMy AccountLoginOrder HistoryGift CardsPayment methodsAccount details
0
Terms of Service and Privacy PolicyHome>Terms of Service and Privacy PolicyPRIVACY POLICYWhen you check out of our store you will be providing us with information that we need to process your order. All of that information is completely private and solely for order processing and shipping. If you sign up for our mailing list we will use your email for that purpose and for no other purpose. You may opt out at any time from that mailing list. All the information that we collect is done so under SSL, a standard internet security measure. Any data that we store about you is kept behind a secure firewall and is not accessible to the public in any way.GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONSYour use of this website is expressly subject to the following Terms of Service and Conditions of Sale (“Terms and Conditions”). If you do not agree with any of these Terms and Conditions, do not access or otherwise use this website or any information or materials contained on this site. Your use of this website shall be deemed to be your agreement to abide by each of the Terms and Conditions set forth herein. These Terms and Conditions may be updated at any time and from time to time with or without notice to you. Your continued use of this website following any such change shall be deemed to indicate your acceptance of any modifications to these Terms and Conditions.The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice. Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law. Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements. You agree that our company and its licensors may make improvements and/or changes in the website content and services or events described in this website, if any, at any time without notice and without liability to you of any kind.You are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws, keeping in mind that access to our website may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If any provision of these Terms and Conditions is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be contrary to law, then such provision(s) shall be construed, as nearly as possible, to reflect the intentions of the parties, with all other provisions remaining in full force and effect. The failure of our company to enforce any right or provision in these Terms and Conditions shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision unless acknowledged and agreed to by our company in writing. The Terms and Conditions, along with our Privacy Policy, comprises the entire agreement between you and us and supersede all prior or contemporaneous negotiations, discussions or agreements, if any, between the parties regarding the subject matter contained herein. These Terms and Conditions are personal to you and you may not transfer, assign, or delegate these Terms and Conditions to anyone without the express written permission of our company. Any attempt by you to assign, transfer, or delegate these Terms and Conditions without the express written permission of our company shall be null and void. These Terms and Conditions will inure to the benefit of our company’s successors, assigns, and licensors. The paragraph headings in these Terms and Conditions, shown in boldface type, are included to help make the agreement easier to read and have no binding effect.Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of the United States. Colorado law and controlling United States federal laws, without regard to the choice or conflicts of law provisions of any jurisdiction, will govern any action related to these Terms and Conditions. You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of the courts located in the State of Colorado, for the resolution of all disputes arising from or related to these Terms and Conditions and/or your use of the website.This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions. All trademarks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offense. From time to time, this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).THE SALE OF ALCOHOLIC BEVERAGESLegal RequirementsWe do not sell alcohol to persons under the age of 21 and make every effort to ensure that alcoholic beverages are not delivered to anyone who is under the age of 21. By using this site, you affirm and acknowledge that you are over the age of 21, that the person placing the order and receiving a shipment of alcoholic beverages from us is over the age of 21 and that receipt of shipments containing alcoholic beverages requires the signature of a person 21 years of age or older who is not intoxicated. You also agree that any alcohol purchased from us is intended for personal consumption and not for resale. If you do not agree with these conditions of use, please do not use this site. If you intentionally or unintentionally misrepresent your age in order to provide alcohol to a person under the age of 21, we will prosecute you fully to the extent allowable by law. As required by the Communications Decency Act of 1996, we hereby notify you that parental control protections (such as computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist you in limiting access to content that may be harmful to minors.Credit Card ChargesOrders are by credit card only. We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover and American Express. The billing address for any such credit card needs to be provided at the time of your order and must be the address on your credit card statement.Errors and OmissionsOccasionally, our listed prices, bottle sizes or quantities may be incorrect. We make every effort to make sure that our product database is accurate, however, in the event any such mistakes occur, we shall be held harmless for any such errors.Disclaimer of WarrantiesALTHOUGH WE ENDEAVOR TO PROVIDE CURRENT, ACCURATE AND RELIABLE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE, WE DO NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE EVENTS OR THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OR ANY USE OF INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE. WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE, OR THE OPERATION OR FUNCTION OF THIS WEBSITE, ANY COMPONENT THEREOF, OR ANY PRODUCTS, SOFTWARE OR SERVICES OFFERED IN CONNECTION THEREWITH, WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE; OR THAT DEFECTS THEREWITH WILL BE CORRECTED; OR THAT THIS SITE OR ITS SERVER IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL ELEMENTS. YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK AND YOU ASSUME FULL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ALL COSTS ASSOCIATED WITH ALL NECESSARY SERVICING OR REPAIR OF ANY EQUIPMENT YOU USE IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE. WE AND OUR SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THIS WEBSITE. THIS WEBSITE CONTENT PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE.Limitation of LiabilityIN NO EVENT SHALL WE AND/OR OUR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THIS WEBSITE, THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS WEBSITE, THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY EVENTS, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF WE OR ANY OF OUR SUPPLIERS HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THIS WEBSITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THIS WEBSITE.Drink ResponsiblyExcessive or irresponsible consumption of alcohol may have personal, social or health consequences. As part of its commitment to responsible consumption, we ensure that communications regarding our products do not show or encourage excessive consumption or misuse of any kind. We are committed to promoting the responsible advertising of our products and encouraging improved advertising standards for the industry as a whole.Follow UsOpens in a new tabOpens in a new tabOpens in a new tabContact UsThe Winery is open for Wine Tasting, Winery Tours & Lunch seven days a week from 11:00am-5:00pm.Address:1946 E 66th Ave, Denver COPhone:(303) 287-5156Opens in your applicationEmail:info@balistreriwine.comOpens in your applicationRecent Posts
High Scoring, NATURAL, Petite Sirah: A Rarity from the CellarAugust 8, 2020/0 Comments
Balistreri Cherry Wine Spritzer RecipeJuly 13, 2020/0 Comments
July 2020 Newsletter | Affordable Natural Wine, Cherry Pies, Smoked Brisket & More!June 30, 2020/0 CommentsSite Search
Search for:
Join Newsletter
Name
First
Last Email*
Copyright © BALISTRERI VINEYARDS 1998 - 2020 | All rights reserved. | Terms of Service & Privacy Policy ×Cart Item added to your cart0 items in the cart ($0.00) Continue Shopping Go To The Cart
You must be 21+ years old and agree with our terms of service to use our website. I am 21+ years old
